Victor David Software Developer

• Lagos, Nigeria

✓ vad.inc8@gmail.com

+234 9072045997

★ https://vaad.netlify.app/



PROFILE

I'm a professional task solving Software Developer from Nigeria. I deliver quality and amazing solutions, with high and proficient skills required.

I'm well versed in team collaboration to formulate and conceptualize corporate web presence. Specialty embracing challenging projects requiring detailed coding changes, search engine-related considerations and security. Integrates knowledge of visual arts to develop functional, appealing, custom-made web products and services.

Building & Designing Software Applications with great user experience is also my expertise.

CONTACT

LinkedIn ra

Github 🛮

WhatsApp □

Twitter ☑

INTERESTS

Coding, Music, Football, Tech research

SKILLS

Frameworks/libraries:

Vue-CLI, Laravel, JQuery, Vuetify, Bootstrap, Express js, Nuxt js

Infrastructure/Databases:

Php, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Mongo dB, Firestore, GraphQl, Node js, Ajax

Programming Languages:

JavaScript, Typescript, Python, C++, Java.

Automation / Tooling:

Git, Docker, Kubernetes., Azure, Gitlab-ci, Circle-ci.

Data Science:

Python (Data Aggregation, Data Manipulation, Data Visualization).

Data Structure and Algorithm:

Python

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering (B.Eng),

Federal University Oye-Ekiti

2019 − 2023 | Ekiti, Nigeria

Certificate degree in software development, SQI ICT ☑

2019 - 2021 | Oyo, Nigeria

Certificate degree in ICT, SQI ICT □

2017 - 2019 | Oyo, Nigeria

High School (FEGO) ☑

2011 - 2017 | Oyo, Nigeria

Victor David 1 / 2

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern, Tecklink

Apr 2022 - present | Tbilisi, Georgia

- » Coded software updates and alterations based on detailed design specifications.
- » Served as an ambitious and motivated apprentice to senior software developers.
- » Worked at an independent level while, also serving as an enthusiastic and effective collaborator.
- » Worked with the backend team and frontend team in developing both backend and frontend for projects with Vue CLI, Node, MongoDb and express (MEVN).
- » Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Html,JavaScript,AJAX and JSON Coding.
- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface
- » Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.

Full Stack Developer, DSC

Apr 2019 - Feb 2021 | Ekiti, Nigeria

- » Worked with project manager, team of developers and customers to resolve technical issues.
- » Developed and maintain documentation related to softwares development processes and systems, including requirements and design documentations.
- » Trained and managed team of developers and discussed issues in order to provide resolution and apply best practices

Web Developer Intern, SQI ICT

Sep 2017 – Jan 2019 | Oyo, Nigeria

- » Planned website development, converting mockups into usable web presence with Html,JavaScript,JAX and JSON Coding.
- »Built some great projects like Banking Applications, PWA Chat Applications, Management System for Schools and Churches using Web technologieslike Php, AJAX, MySQL
- » Employed coding practices based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface

PROJECTS

FuoyeMarket,

connect with your choice sellers. ☑ An Ecommerce website for connecting campus students with their choice sellers

The mightgain 🛮

It's a web application software for providing all social media services

Speedyfame 2

A web application software for improving and promoting sales through the social media.

BSF 🛮

A creative website design for students organization

Topsocial 2

Integrated various payment methods for the web software application.

Vad □

My portfolio website

Github 🛮

Other projects available here on github:

- Web software bank application.
- Php Web chat application (Vchat)
- Data visualization using python
- Data aggregation using python
- Web E-commerce software application.
- C+ Solutions
- JavaScript calculator
- Recharge voucher generator.
- Audio player using JavaScript.
- Blog using Node, express, ejs, mongodb.
- Web based chat app using Web socket, Node, Express, Mongo db.
- A school online store project.
- Bar code generator using Php

Victor David 2 / 2